This medicine's pain
cuts deep into the bones.
Your Highness,
you must endure it a little longer.
Your Highness, you still need
to stay in the medicinal bath
and soak for another hour.
Thank you for your trouble, Yunhuai.
You seem
to be different from before.
How so?
You have been afflicted
by a strange poison since childhood.
It has been incurable for a long time.
Although you sought medical treatment,
you had a carefree attitude, as if
you were indifferent to life and death.
You often said
that the remaining five or six years
were enough to find the person
who poisoned you.
After that,
you would travel the world
with no set date of return.
But today,
you are so eager to be cured.
This is the first time
I've seen you like this.
If not for your skilled treatment
back then,
I certainly wouldn't have lived
to this day.
Every treatment
feels like my bones are being scraped
and my flesh is being cut.
You always praise me for my strong will,
but every time,
the pain is so unbearable
that I want to end my own life.
Your Highness,
you must not think that way.
But now,
I truly want to live a little longer.
I've discovered
that there are indeed some things
I haven't experienced
that I yearn for.
=Blossoms of Power=
(Adapted from the novel, After My
Bloom, All Flowers Wither by Jin Huang)
=Episode 6=
Your Highness.
While on patrol,
I intercepted a secret letter.
Your Highness,
after you and the Crown Prince
finished viewing
the Starvine Moss together,
you can still read a book here
so calmly.
Did you get to know the Crown Prince
a little better this time?
He's very good.
So good
that it makes me even more guarded.
How did you get so soaked?
They say kittens are afraid of water,
but this one is different.
The harder it rains,
the more it runs outside.
Find a cloth to dry it off.
I'll go get one.
Come.
Your Highness,
Prince Lie is here to see you.
I won't see him.
He said
you will definitely change your mind
after seeing this.
(Military Seal)
The Anxi defense map?
This map is a core military secret
that the Duke of Wei's Manor
has guarded for generations.
It marks the strengths and weaknesses
of the seven defense lines in northwest,
the troop deployments
in sixteen fortresses,
as well as hidden granaries
and water sources.
If this map were to fall
into enemy hands,
it would be like completely exposing
the vital points of northwest frontier.
You are right.
Even if this map doesn't fall
into enemy hands,
the crime of losing it alone is severe.
For losing a national treasure,
the responsible official
will be executed by waist-chopping,
and three generations of their family
will be exiled 1,500 km.
If this matter were
to reach the imperial court,
I'm afraid
it would be a devastating disaster
for our Duke of Wei's Manor.
(A defense map)
(is enough to stir up turmoil
in the court.)
(It could bring eternal damnation
upon the Shen family.)
(I must protect northwest)
(in order to protect myself.)
Will you see Prince Lie, Your Highness?
No.
Your Highness.
Prince Lie doesn't know
if this map is real or fake right now.
If I see him,
it will confirm that the map is real.
Return it to Prince Lie.
Yes.
I'll write a letter to Father.
In a moment, you will take
this letter to Hua Fuhai.
Have him deliver it
to Father as quickly as possible.
Once Father knows,
the defense layout will be changed.
This real map will become a fake one.
Your Highness.
The Commandery Princess asked Hua Fuhai
to deliver this letter to northwest
as quickly as possible.
Ask Hua Fuhai to use a gyrfalcon
to get it to northwest
as soon as possible.
Aren't you going to take a look?
Your Highness,
this is a serious matter.
About this Hua Fuhai...
It's fine.
In this letter, I used the secret code I
share with my father and brother.
Even if he reads this letter,
he won't be able to understand it.
If she gave the letter to Hua Fuhai,
she must be certain
that no one else can understand it.
Something major must have happened.
Find out what it is.
Yes.
Your Highness, please leave.
The Commandery Princess
didn't say anything?
Her Highness just said three words.
"Not seeing you."
(Why won't she see me?)
(Could the map be a fake?)
That's enough.
Yes.
I'll only ask you once.
Where did
this map come from?
You're a tough one indeed.
What brings you here, Your Highness?
I thought about it all night.
Your move of creating something
from nothing,
a secret feint,
was truly brilliant.
If I were to give this
to my father today,
what do you think
the consequences would be?
You've gone to such great lengths.
Can we get down to business now?
Let's speak in private.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to eat you.
(Crystal Clear as Water)
Are you hungry?
We didn't come here to eat.
There's no need to beat around the bush.
What is it that you really want?
On the day of the hunt,
I told you,
if you marry me,
I will only marry you in this lifetime.
Do you remember?
So,
you're using that map to threaten me
into agreeing to marry you?
I know the map I have is real.
Yesterday, you bluffed
and bought yourself some time.
It's a pity
that northwest
is thousands of miles away.
Are you trying
to use my father and brother,
and the entire northwest army
to blackmail me?
Then I can give you my answer right now.
Impossible.
Move.
Your Highness, please conduct yourself
with dignity.
Dignity?
Didn't you know
before you even came to the capital
that I have a fiery temper,
and I'm perverse and ruthless?
I've never been a gentleman.
I know the Duke has his heart
set on me as his ideal son-in-law.
I'll ask you one more time.
Will you marry me?
I will not.
Shen Xihe, stop right there!
Could all of this
be a play you've written
and directed yourself, Your Highness?
What do you mean?
How could the Anxi defense map,
from thousands of miles away,
be intercepted by the Imperial Guard
in the imperial capital
and end up in your hands?
It seems you're unaware of this matter.
Then it must be the work of that
resourceful and decisive brother
of yours.
You use such tactics
to seek my hand in marriage.
If my father found out,
would he still see you
as his ideal choice?
Today,
whatever you choose to do with this map,
do as you please.
(Prince Xin's Manor)
Changqing,
did you send someone
to steal the Anxi defense map
and then put it in my hands?
The Anxi defense map
concerns the safety of our borders.
Although I didn't steal the map,
I did arrange for someone
to deliver it to you.
Why?
Do you know
the Commander-in-Chief of Hexi,
Ye Qi?
Isn't he just Consort Liang's cousin?
Ye Qi covets the title of Duke of Wei.
He bribed a protector-general
under Shen Yueshan
and stole the defense map.
But our men intercepted it.
Since you already intercepted the map,
you should have sent it
back to northwest.
Why did you let it circulate
in the imperial capital?
Naturally, I wanted to help you
win the one you love.
I've said it before.
I don't need your help.
I will pursue the one I love myself.
Relying on schemes and tricks
is not what I call sincerity.
What can be seen
is called sincerity.
What cannot be seen
is called unrequited love.
By the way,
with your straightforward personality,
how did you figure out I was behind it?
I met with Commandery Princess Zhaoning.
She was the one who guessed
that you were behind all of this.
I've never met her before.
How does she understand
my thoughts so well?
Last time,
my plan to retrieve the Rouge Ledger
was completely seen through by her.
It's the same this time.
She easily...
saw right through me.
(Taiji Hall)
Recently,
rumors have been spreading
throughout the court,
saying that Shen Yueshan
has lost the Anxi defense map.
My dear ministers,
have you heard of this?
I have heard something of it.
Your Majesty,
the defense map is of vital importance
to the state.
This is a serious matter.
Although the rumors are hard to verify,
there's no smoke without fire.
I believe
we should immediately summon
Shen Yueshan to the capital
to give an explanation.
I believe that is absolutely
out of the question.
If someone is intentionally
creating a diversion
to lure the tiger from the mountain,
and northwest is attacked
with no one there to command,
what shall we do then?
Indeed.
Northwest cannot be left unguarded.
But the Duke of Wei is indeed a suspect.
What should be done in this situation?
(Dong Biquan, Minister of Revenue)
Your Majesty,
I have received reliable information
that the Anxi defense map
is in the hands of Prince Lie.
Changying,
is this true?
Reporting to Your Majesty,
I do not know where Minister Dong
heard such a ridiculous rumor.
If the defense map were
in my possession,
I would have presented it
to you immediately.
The Imperial Guard
has never intercepted any spy,
nor has Prince Lie
tortured anyone in prison.
Since you are so certain,
why not present your evidence?
I am willing to face him.
Changying,
I ask you again.
Did you really not intercept
the defense map?
Reporting to Your Majesty,
I did not.
Good.
Prince Lie said he did not.
Then he did not.
My ministers,
there is no need to chase shadows.
Dispatch someone immediately
to northwest
to investigate this matter thoroughly.
I trust
there will be a conclusion soon.
(Duke of Wei's Manor)
Your Highness,
news has arrived from northwest.
The defense map has been safely returned
to Shen Yueshan.
Prince Lie not only
stopped pressuring you,
but also protected northwest
at the risk of deceiving His Majesty.
His feelings for you are truly deep.
Although he is unruly,
he is ultimately good-natured.
But as long as
the map thief isn't caught,
the crisis in northwest
will not end.
Your Highness,
Hua Fuhai sent a secret letter.
He says
he is greatly honored to have your trust
and is willing to serve you loyally.
Commander-in-Chief of Hexi?
Ye Qi, Commander-in-Chief of Hexi.
He has been in charge of Liangzhou
for over a decade
and knows northwest
like the back of his hand.
With the defense map lost,
if His Majesty holds
the Duke accountable,
he is the most likely person
to take over the northwest Army.
I see.
Hua Fuhai is trying to tell me
that the map thief
is one of Ye Qi's men.
Mo Yuan, send a message
to Father immediately.
He must investigate this thoroughly.
Yes.
The court discussed it this morning,
and we only heard the news at lunch.
Yet Hua Fuhai
has already sent us the answer.
It must be that Tagara Incense
that made Hua Fuhai act this way.
It seems he has everything
under control.
Your Highness,
don't you think
we're always
at a disadvantage like this?
Go on.
Regarding Ye Qi,
you leaked the
information to the Commandery Princess.
But on the surface,
it looks like Prince Lie saved her
and protected northwest.
This way,
she will surely be more moved,
and the Duke will favor him even more.
Changying has no chance.
Your Highness, why are you so certain?
Changqing and Changying
share a deep bond.
The Duke thinks
Changqing is exceptionally talented
and most likely to inherit the throne.
Then, Changying would be second
only to one and above all others.
The Commandery Princess would also
avoid the conflicts of the harem.
The Duke
has chosen the best path
for his precious daughter.
It's just a pity
that to achieve his goal,
Changqing would actually use
the defense map to threaten her.
Tian Yuan,
give the order.
Find a way to let the Duke know
that the Commandery Princess
was threatened.
Yes.
You are wise, Your Highness.
By the way,
didn't Zhao Zhenghao say
he already had a lead
on the source of the strange poison?
What's the progress now?
Recently, a foreign merchant from the
Western Regions did come to the capital.
He specializes in selling illicit drugs,
including many strange poisons.
However,
this person is cunning
and difficult to find.
Vice Minister Cui is already
investigating in secret.
Right under the Emperor's nose,
someone dares to openly smuggle drugs!
Investigate it!
- Yes.
The Imperial Guard?
What are you doing here?
It seems we are quite fated.
We even run into each other
while investigating a case.
What case are you investigating?
A foreign merchant
from the Western Regions
who has two lives on his hands
from robbery and murder.
And you, Vice Minister Cui?
It's none of your business.
This foreign merchant is truly cunning
and meticulous in his actions.
But he can't escape
his weakness for ladies.
My informant told me
he's going to a tavern by the river
for some fun.
If you're willing, Vice Minister Cui,
you can join me in capturing him.
Long time no see.
Indeed.
Come, come, have a seat inside.
Let me accompany you inside.
Why are you staring at me?
I'm looking at the four big words
on your forehead,
"I am an officer."
You don't look like a patron at all.
No songstress or drinking. You might
as well just announce to the world
that we're here to arrest someone.
You were the one who told me
that after staking this place out
for days,
the foreign merchant
would definitely show up today.
Otherwise, why would I be with you...
in a place like this?
You say that
as if it's your first time here.
It really is your first time?
The only pure and innocent man
in the world.
What's so hard about it?
I'll just teach you.
Don't touch me.
Don't be ungrateful.
I'm teaching you
how to get into character.
You can just tell me.
Loosen your clothes.
A grown man being so indecisive.
Keep your hands to yourself.
I know him.
Young Master Cui.
Yes, that's him.
It's him. It's definitely him.
Let's go.
If someone recognizes you,
your reputation will be ruined.
Where do we go?
They've blocked the door.
Go that way.
Get up.
Hurry, let's go.
- Young Master Cui!
You have the wrong person.
They jumped into the river?
Good thing we ran fast.
It's okay. We're fine now. Here.
Wait.
Don't worry.
Next time I set a trap,
we'll definitely catch
that foreign merchant.
Hold on.
Why are you just taking
someone else's things?
An official is investigating a case.
I'm just commandeering
a piece of clothing.
Why make such a big deal out of it?
Do not commit an evil act,
no matter how small.
As a court official,
you knowingly broke the law
and you show no remorse.
This is truly unreasonable.
I'll take my leave.
I was afraid you'd catch a cold.
Put it on.
Then you should also...
Farewell.
(Xu Qing, Abbot of Fahua Temple)
Your Highness, the Jati flower incense
blended by you
is pure, rich, and elegant.
It's truly extraordinary.
We have been trying to create a superior
Buddhist incense without success.
Thank you, Your Highness,
for lending your aid.
You flatter me, Master.
I am willing to do my part.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Master, may I ask,
did Commandery Princess Zhaoning
come here today
to specifically blend
the Jati flower incense
for the Buddha statue?
The last time the Empress Dowager
brought Her Highness to offer incense,
it coincided with our temple's attempt
to blend this incense.
However, we could not
get the method right.
We asked Her Highness for some guidance.
The fragrance turned out to be superior.
Therefore, today,
we invited Her Highness again.
So you're saying
Commandery Princess Zhaoning
is an expert in incense making?
Right now,
not just in the entire imperial capital,
but even throughout all of Daxing,
it would be hard to find her equal.
There are extraordinary people
in this world, uniquely gifted.
Incense making requires
a certain spiritual gift.
A natural talent like Her Highness's...
I have only ever seen it
in one other person in my entire life.
Are you referring to
my princess consort?
Precisely, it's your princess consort.
It's strange, now that you mention it.
Commandery Princess Zhaoning
has come a long way from northwest,
but her incense-blending technique
is identical to that
of the Prince Xin's Consort.
There's not the slightest difference.
Your Highness,
what do you think of this piece?
Qingqing.
Someone like you,
a proper and elegant lady,
could never do something
so free-spirited and unrestrained.
She is not you.
Over there.
Greetings, Commandery Princess Zhaoning.
- Greetings, Your Highness.
I was at the temple today
to pay respects to my late wife.
I happened to run into you.
May I have a word with you in private?
What is it you wish to discuss,
Your Highness?
You can speak freely here.
A few days ago,
His Majesty gathered all the princes
at the hunting grounds
to profess their feelings for you.
At the time, you did not make a choice.
Changying
is my only full brother.
I would like to, on his behalf,
ask for your hand in marriage once more.
Ask on his behalf?
Although Changying can be
a bit impatient and arrogant,
he is a sincere person
with a resolute heart.
His feelings for you are genuine.
That is why I have the audacity to ask.
If you agree,
Changying will,
for the rest of his life,
never love another.
If we can unite our families
through marriage,
then regarding the future situation
in northwest,
whatever you and Duke Wei desire,
I, Changqing, will also
do my utmost to ensure it happens.
- Greetings, Your Highness.
At ease.
Your Highness,
why are you at Fahua Temple?
I heard the ginkgo trees
at Fahua Temple are quite lovely.
I came specially
to see for myself.
Why are you collecting ginkgo leaves,
Commandery Princess?
What are they for?
To make a medicinal pillow
to help with sleep.
Really?
I often have trouble sleeping at night.
I wonder if you
could share the method with me.
In that case, I will make one for you.
Thank you.
What?
Do you want one, too?
After I get the method from her,
I'll make one for you with my own hands.
You are frail.
I wouldn't dare trouble you.
You should rest well.
You're very considerate.
But this is something I can manage.
Please, take your time, Your Highnesses.
It's getting late.
I should be returning home.
Enjoy your stroll in the garden,
Your Highness.
I shall take my leave as well.
Tian Yuan.
Have someone sort through these leaves,
pick out the best ones,
and give them
to the Commandery Princess.
Yes.
Guards.
(Boundless Compassion, Pure Inaction)
Your Highness.
Investigate
Commandery Princess Zhaoning thoroughly.
Everything related to her,
every single detail,
no matter how minor,
must not be overlooked.
Yes.
(East Palace)
Your Highness,
the Commandery Princess was so quick
to send the pillow over.
And she made it herself.
Tian Yuan,
don't you think
that she has been
a bit closer to me lately?
More than just a bit closer.
It's a huge step forward.
The way she looks at you, there's
a hint of tenderness in her eyes.
This is unprecedented.
It's a look she reserves only for you.
Your Highness,
regarding the case
of the Anxi defense map,
Duke Wei started his investigation
with Ye Qi
and has clarified many suspicious points
and gathered evidence.
He sent men to report each finding
to His Majesty.
His Majesty was very displeased.
During the court session,
in front of all the civil
and military officials,
he reprimanded Ye Qi
for his malicious intentions.
To show his loyalty,
Ye Qi kowtowed on the floor
until his head was bleeding,
solemnly vowing
that the matter had nothing
to do with him.
How did Father deal with him?
His Majesty sentenced Ye Qi
to exile in Tongzhou.
He's to be a slave for life.
He's forbidden
from entering the capital forever.
He brought it upon himself.
With Ye Qi's downfall,
the lucrative position
of Commander-in-Chief of Hexi is vacant.
At court tomorrow,
there will surely be an endless argument
over who will replace him.
Your Highness, what are your plans?
Let Xiao Changqing's man take it.
The Commander-in-Chief of Hexi
controls the northwest corridor.
Prince Xin has had his eye
on this position for a long time.
In the future,
he can also help Prince Lie
pursue the Commandery Princess.
In this matter,
Changqing and Changying
benefit the most.
The Duke of Wei will surely think
that they were the ones
pulling the strings.
Changying is already deeply in love
with the Commandery Princess.
And Changying,
even while mourning his late wife,
didn't forget to propose marriage.
Since they're so persistent
about the Commandery Princess,
we might as well crush
their foolish hopes completely.
(Taiji Hall)
By His Majesty's decree.
The bandit infestation in Fengzhou
has been eradicated,
and the people's livelihood
has been stabilized.
General Rong Ce of Anbei
deserves the highest merit.
Effective immediately, he is reassigned
as Commander-in-Chief of Hexi.
Thus it is decreed.
The one who was just promoted
is your maternal uncle, isn't he?
Noble Consort Rong's elder brother
was enfeoffed as the Duke of Ying.
Now, her younger brother has been
promoted to Commander-in-Chief of Hexi.
Truly two heroes from one family.
This is cause for celebration.
My humble congratulations
to you two princes.
This bandit problem
that has been going on for half a year
happened to coincide with the vacancy
of Commander-in-Chief of Hexi position.
And it just so happened
to be resolved then.
What timely news.
Very timely.
Perhaps a month ago,
or even longer,
it was already taken care of.
They were just waiting
for the right time to report it.
Exactly.
I shall take my leave.
Minister Hu, wait for me.
Regarding the bandit suppression,
I did not dare to report it rashly.
I intended to send a message
to Your Highness
and await your decision.
Who would have known
that the royal uncle
would submit a memorial behind my back?
It was my failure
to handle the matter properly.
I ask for Your Highness's punishment.
This has nothing to do with you.
You may leave.
Yes.
Changqing.
With our uncle now in the position
of Commander-in-Chief of Hexi,
we have made many enemies at court.
Furthermore, Shen Yueshan will suspect
that we were the masterminds.
This will affect your marriage
to Commandery Princess Zhaoning.
All of this
seems like a coincidence,
but it's actually very strange.
There must be someone behind the scenes,
secretly manipulating things.
Given Xiao Changqing's
cunning and schemes,
if he were behind this,
he would have done it
without anyone noticing.
Even if he wanted
to install his own man,
it wouldn't be this one,
an uncle
with such obvious nepotistic ties.
Looking at the whole situation,
not only did he not gain any advantage,
but he has instead attracted a lot
of jealousy and resentment.
He's become a clear target for everyone.
Your Highness, you mean
someone is secretly
targeting the two brothers?
The General of Anbei position
vacated by Rong Ce,
who filled it?
Someone was transferred from
the Imperial Guard to fill the vacancy.
Then the position that opened up
in the Imperial Guard,
who filled that?
The Embroidered Envoy.
Could it be
that Tagara Incense again?
He can silently
infiltrate the Emperor's most rigorous
and tight-knit circle of power.
And he's also an enemy
of the Xiao Changqing brothers.
Could it be...
He is a member of the royal family?
Reporting to Young Master Bu.
I've already notified
all the Shunan merchant guilds.
Once that foreign merchant
selling illicit drugs appears,
he will be watched closely.
I guarantee
he'll have nowhere to run.
He entered from the Shunan border
and is doing business
in the imperial capital.
He definitely can't avoid
the Shunan merchant guilds.
You're an important figure
in the guilds.
Don't let me down.
- Young Master Bu.
Young Master.
It's been so long since your last visit.
I thought
you had forgotten about me.
Your "Phoenix Tree Song" lingers
for three days.
I won't find another like you
in the entire capital.
Young Master.
Did you guys hear?
I heard
that Cui Jinbai was having a secret
rendezvous at the riverside tavern.
He was caught and fled in a panic.
He jumped into the river.
A secret meeting at a tavern
is no big deal.
Why would he risk his life over it?
That Cui Jinbai is such a phony.
He acts so aloof and pure.
I think people like him
are the most hypocritical.
They're not as true to their nature
as you and I.
He's all sanctimonious in public,
but in reality,
he's even wilder than we are.
How interesting.
Come, Hu, please.
- Come on.
What are you doing?
You... What are you doing?
You two were fighting in a tavern,
disturbing the peace.
According to the laws of our dynasty...
What fight?
With him? I was just
teaching him a lesson, one-sidedly.
I...
So you're admitting
to relying on your
superior martial arts skills
to bully others?
He deserved it.
Why did he deserve it?
If you don't tell me,
I can only handle this
according to the law.
According to the laws of Daxing,
those who provoke trouble
and engage in brawls
shall receive 20 to 50 strikes
with the rod.
Guards!
Hu Yu, 20 strikes.
Bu Shulin,
50 strikes.
- Wait.
- Yes.
Why does he get 20 and I get 50?
Because you are an imperial guard.
Knowingly breaking the law
is a more severe crime.
If I weren't helping you
investigate the foreign merchant,
would I be hanging
around a place like that?
I worked tirelessly,
day and night, to find clues for you.
And this is how you treat me,
Vice Minister Cui?
Captain Bu,
investigating a case is one thing,
but you broke the law.
These are two separate matters.
Fine.
I'll accept it.
After all, I do admire
this impartiality of yours.
Suffering a little for one of our own
is worth it.
Take them away!
Let's go.
Let go.
You see that he's frail
and want to find a backup.
You're playing both sides.
Never mind playing both sides.
What if I were to explore
a few more options?
Among all the princes,
Prince Lie is a rare military talent.
I just saw that Xihe seems to admire
Prince Lie quite a bit.
You're from northwest.
Could it be that you prefer
more masculine men?
♪I've hidden so many words♪
♪Too reluctant to tell you♪
♪So never uncover♪
♪The sand that slips away
with one grasp♪
♪The flower that withers
after one bloom♪
♪Silently buried deep inside my heart♪
♪Every answer I gave♪
♪Was both bittersweet and absurd♪
♪Hiding my tear-filled eyes
when I hurt you♪
♪How hard it truly was?♪
♪The wounds that healed
with just a little comfort♪
♪The lies made whole
with a single embrace♪
♪Pretending to be brave
as if I'd never been hurt♪
♪It's a shame I never could♪
♪Give you a moon in return♪
♪With the same open heart you loved me♪
♪I've crossed the wasteland of memories♪
♪Never knowing I was lost♪
♪Why don't you take me away?♪
♪Lead me out of this endless game
of hide-and-seek♪
♪You'll never♪
♪Know how much I long to, long to♪